Hello everyone. Welcome back to today's new tutorial topic. So today I'm back for here the post-grid
SQL tutorial series. So here we are just explored for how to fetch data for the post-grid
SQL table using for the various methods and the queries, okay. So first of all here
simply explained for the post-grid SQL fetch data and table is a fundamental aspect of data
management. And you can retrieve the specific query code filter data perform various operations
using the SQL query. So here in this session now just directly jump into here the practical
implementation of the fetch data, okay. So first question for here I can just solve how to use the
fetch data in the post-grid SQL. So now I can just go for here so I can already
create a table in my database in the details and the listed below. So now I can just copy this
table. So first of all here I can just select and start and also type for here the from and
now just first of all here I create the table name just start with the article okay.
So now just type the article okay. So here open perfectly and here now just select and execute.
You can see here the table all the information okay. So the article ID, the article title and the
published data okay. So you can see here perfectly and now it is completely open in the article table
has the row and run perfectly in this query. And now in this session we'll do it for another example.
So now just let's run the following query let's fetch the first three rows of the article table okay.
And here we'll use the sorted vertical ID in the ascending order okay.
So now just open the another query and first of all let type for this is the
start and from type the articles and then going to the next step here I can use the
order by okay. So order by the article I okay.
So I'll just perfectly type the article underscore ID okay.
And the next step here we're going to do this is the ascending order and their next step here
we're going to use the fetch data. So first we'll write here this is the fetch then
the first field okay the first three rows only. So here it is defined perfectly and now
just select okay then execute and destroy it and here is the first field this is the
third query and this is the first query and here first the row is clear table delete query and
then inside query this is the first three row okay and here variable and insert is the values is the
options first in the fetch query okay. So now just bring the next step and here I will create the
complete place and we'll store the product of it and here I'll now show because the whole piece
for the query is okay. So now we'll go to another way and just keep for the first three rows
and now I can fetch for the next three rows. So now just go into the again list here and type
so first of all here I can use the offset okay. So now we can make this
query and here first of all type this is the offset for the three row okay
the offset three row and next step again again define fetch for the first three rows only okay.
So here just simply type this statement for here the first three rows and you can see here
it is used just only and you can check for the statement perfectly show the output okay. So here
I can simply remove this and now just check for another key table and first of all here select
then ID then also here the type the first name and also here the last name okay. So define
for the last name and now here choose for the employee statement okay. So define perfectly
describe the employee table okay. So here now in this session I can just select and execute
and this order you can see here perfectly see that put so first on the
green byte next on first name and the last name okay. So here this session is completely done
and in this phase data set completely working and show the output for the display okay.
So I hope you perfectly understand this session. So thank you for watching and happy coding okay.